There's more than one way to shoot yourself
Overnight is a documentary film directed by Mark Brian Smith.
Alternately hilarious and horrifying, Overnight chronicles one
man's misadventures of making a Hollywood movie.
It starts out as a rags to riches story as Troy Duffy, a Boston-bred
bartender, sells his first screenplay for The Boondock Saints.
Self, played by Troy Duffy.
Self, played by Billy Connolly.
Self, played by Norman Reedus.
Self, played by Jake Busey.
Self, played by Emmanuelle Béart.
Self, played by Vincent D'Onofrio.
Overnight is a 2003 American documentary film by
Tony Montana and Mark Brian Smith.
The film details several years in the life of filmmaker and musician Troy Duffy, the
writer-director of The Boondock Saints (1999), and was filmed at his request.
Duffy is presented as a victim of his own ego: as the documentary progresses and his fortunes fade during the troubled production and
distribution of The Boondock Saints, he becomes increasingly abusive to his friends, relatives and business partners.
According to co-director Montana, "Troy seemed to revel in the
attention of Hollywood's lights and our cameras.
Only three times during the production did he ask not to be filmed.
It was on those occasions that he threatened us."
The film explores themes of rags to riches, filmmaking, riches to rags.